Guide to the Kensinger Jones Papers, 1934-2001 and undated RL.00648
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1959-1996 and undated
  - 16mm films, 1962-1980 and undated
    - 7. Creativity film, Horse and Fiddle, and RIBENA. Doctor, Campbell-Ewald and Peter Robinson Studio, 1962 and 1973-1974 (Box 82)
    - 8. Duncan Hines, [undated] (Box 82)
    - 9. Duncan Hines Cake, and MBA, [undated] (Box 82)
    - 10. Explorers Boy Scouts of America, [undated] (Box 82)
    - 11. Farewell from D.P. Brother, 1970-1971 (Box 82)
    - 12. GMC, [undated] (Box 83)
    - 13. Importance of Being Interesting, 1965 (also used in Hong Kong in 1975) (Box 83)
    - 14. Julie McKnight Ken in Pabst Beer, [undated] (Box 83)
    - 15. NADA/TVB Presentations, Ford Institute, Wilding Advertising and Auto Dealer Award Winning TV Commercials, 1978 (Box 83)
    - 16. NADA, New Orleans, including log, 1980 (Box 84)
    - 17. Oldsmobile commercials, including log, 1970-1973 (Box 84)
    - 18. Pfizer commercial, Terramycin, Dave Livingston pig farmer, [undated] (Box 84)
    - 19. Progress Report, [undated] (Box 84)
    - 20. [Untitled], [undated] (Box 84)
    - 21. Whatever Happened to Mrs. Momiyama? [undated] (Box 85)
- Oversize Materials, 1948-2002 and undated
  Advertisements, awards, books, brochures, calendars, cartoons, certificates, clippings, photographs, posters, scrapbooks, storyboards, and teaching materials documenting Jones's advertising and academic careers. Arranged alphabetically by type of material, followed by bound books. At the end are materials in an oversize cabinet.
  - Advertisements: Oldsmobile ads from Leo Burnett Company, 1971-1973, 1 folder (Box 86)
  - Advertisements: Oldsmobile ads from D.P. Brother, 1967-1970, 1 folder (Box 86)
  - Advertisements: ads for AC Spark Plugs, Pillsbury, and Union 76 from Leo Burnett Company, 1972-1973, 1 folder (Box 86)
  - Advertisements: miscellaneous ads for Better Business Bureau, Singapore, and Volvo, 1973 and undated, 1 folder (Box 86)
  - Advertisements: collateral brochures for Oldsmobile 1973 and 1974 and for Singapore Handicraft Centre, 1976, 1 folder (Box 86)
  - Awards and certificates, to Jones and from Jones to his students, ca. 1982-1987 (Box 86)
  - Brochure by and about William R. Biggs/Gilmore Associates, Who? In Kalamazoo? 1983 (Box 86)
  - Brochures by and about Campbell-Ewald, Co., 1963-1967, 4 items (Box 86)
  - Calendar: Made in Michigan: Nostalgic Advertising from a Bygone Era, Michigan History Magazine Wall Calendar, 1995 (Box 86)
  - Cartoons and drawings given to Jones, mostly undated, 1 folder (Box 86)
  - Clipping, "Local Man's Papers Now a Collection at Duke University", 2002 (Box 86)
  - Clippings: Kensinger Jones: Putting it all Together, feature article in The Grand Rapids Press Wonderland, July 31, 1983 (Box 86)
  - Clippings: St. Louis History Over the Air, feature article on Jones in St. Louis, St. Louis Post-Dispatch, June 6, 1948 (Box 86)
  - Clippings: issues of China Daily and China Pictorial, 1988 (Box 86)
  - Course materials: student project, "Felpausch Campaign," photographs, posters, and clippings from Advertising 441, Fall 1984 (Box 86)
  - Scrapbooks of Jones's career, 1957-1962, 6 volumes (Box 87)
  - Scrapbooks of Jones's career, 1963-1971, 5 volumes (Box 88)
  - Une Americaine a Paris, Campbell-Ewald storyboard for Chevrolet, 1959 (Box 89)
  - The Best Advertisements from Reader's Digest, 1955-1961, Random-House, Inc., 1962 (Box 89)
  - The Forward Look, a report from McCann-Erickson, Inc. on "activities pursued for the Chrysler Corporation during the past 20 months," 1956 Jan. 30 (Box 89)
  - Reaching for the Stars: A Book for the Silver Anniversary, Leo Burnett Company, Inc., presented to Kensinger Jones, 1960 August 5 (Box 90)
  - Reaching for the Stars: A Record of Five Years, 1960-1965, Leo Burnett Company, Inc., 1965 (Box 90)
  - Reaching for the Stars: A Record of Five Years, 1965-1970, Leo Burnett Company, Inc., 1970 (Box 90)
  - Singapore, Singapore Tourist Promotion Board, inscribed by Jones to his mother, 1974 Sept. 9 (Box 90)
  - Advertisements for Jardines created by Jones, ca. 1970s, 4 items (Oversize-folder Folder 1)
  - Cartoons of colleagues, family, and friends [by Jones? undated], 3 items (Oversize-folder Folder 1)
  - Collage posters inscribed to Jones regarding his move to and stay in Australia, ca. 1973, 2 items (Oversize-folder Folder 1)
  - Historical Guide Note No. 49, desk blotter with inscription to Jones (Oversize-folder Folder 1)